[{"answer": "I'm doing well, Piers.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Jesse, how are you?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "You are looking very well.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "How re you?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "Yes, that's true.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "I will.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "How does that work?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "We're already fascists, Piers.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "You're basically endorsing a form of fascism, aren't you?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "Well, I guess that -- here's what I thought when I read your book.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Why is it just one way?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Well, you can still -- you can turn the Democrats and Republicans into special interests, which is what they are anyway.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "How do you actually have a government that works if everyone is an independent?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "No, not necessarily.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "These would be independents formerly known as Democrats and Republicans, wouldn't they?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Go on.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "You know why?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "You know why?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Well, my reaction, it doesn't matter.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "When you hear the president and Republican nominee going at it like this, given the state of economy, what's your reaction?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I think it's awful.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "I won't be boycotting them.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "So presumably you'll be boycotting FOX and MSNBC on your book tour, will you, Jesse?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "-- will have me on.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, he is pulling them out.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "He has?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Well, I guess he is.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "He's pulling them out, isn't he?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, I'll give you a scenario.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "What would you do with Iran?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "You don't think --", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "So the U.S. -- the U.S. is definitely threatened by these countries in what way?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Well, I think that's what -- the defense basically filed that motion today.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I don't think it's damaged.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Is it damaged at all by the fact that quite a few of the boys who are now men obviously have also filed civil complaints, so there is a potential financial incentive here?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "I saw when Jason Carroll was talking about the defense strategy, you shaking your head vigorously there.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "Don't they have some right to some recompense to help them deal with the abuse as they go forward?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "I don't understand what the defense strategy is.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "You clearly don't make a lot of that, right?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "It is classic grooming behaviors, isn't it, we're looking at?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I think both sides probably think this is going to advantage them.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "What's that all about?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Well, I've been in public service just about all of my adult life, in addition to the time my wife and I spent running a small business.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Why are you running?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "Well, that's a good question.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "What do you say to those who say, you know, you're no spring chicken and the young guy should get a run?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's got a good message there.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "What did you think when you heard that?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "I think that's the distraction my opponent has tried to use to move us away from what's really important to the people of Arizona.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "Well, when it comes to the November election, I will support the president.", "docId": "120611pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Just for the purposes of clarification, are you a big supporter of the president?", "qSentId": 585}]